database = [
    {
        question: 'Which gas do we need to take into the blood in the lungs?',
        optionA: 'Carbon Dioxide',
        optionB: 'Oxgyen',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which gas can produce droplets on a cold window?',
        optionA: 'Water Vapour',
        optionB: 'Carbon Dioxide',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Food is mainly digested in the _____.',
        optionA: 'Stomach',
        optionB: 'Liver',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which substance causes the addiction to cigarettes?',
        optionA: 'Nicotine',
        optionB: 'Carbon Monoxide',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the main role of the red blood cells?',
        optionA: 'To heal wounds',
        optionB: 'To transport oxygen',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'When hydrochloric acid is added to iron it begins to ______.',
        optionA: 'Rust',
        optionB: 'Disintegrate',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the foods is the best source for Vitamin C?',
        optionA: 'Oranges',
        optionB: 'Eggs',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which substance from cigarettes may cause lung cancer?',
        optionA: 'Carbon Monoxide',
        optionB: 'Tar',
        answer: 'B'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which substance from cigarettes is carried instead of oxygen in the bloodstream?',
        optionA: 'Carbon Monoxide',
        optionB: 'Nicotine',
        answer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which organ is affected the most if you eat too much?',
        optionA: 'Lungs',
        optionB: 'Heart',
        answer: 'B'
    }
]